(Raj:)Well, that's that.
(Raj:)The room's compromised.
(Raj:)They'll have to change
all the filters,
(Raj:)probably shut it down
for weeks.
(Howard:)You were right. Go ahead,
call Building Services.
(Howard:)Tell them it was my fault.
No, we're both to blame.
(Leonard:)You know, let me take
the heat on this one.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Yeah, just leave me out of it.
(Raj:)You know if they come here
and see crap everywhere,
(Raj:)they're just gonna
blame the Indian guy.
(ringtone playing)
(Leonard(on phone):)Hey. I'm sorry,
we're still here.
(Leonard(on phone):)Is everything okay?
(Penny:)It's kind of boring.
(Penny:)Although it did get exciting
for a minute
(Penny:)when Amy inhaled a wool ball.
(Penny:)How much longer
do you think you'll be?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)There's still
a bird in here.
(Leonard:)We are gonna get in
a ton of trouble.
(Penny:)Honey, it's Christmas Eve.
Who even knows you're in there?
(Leonard:)No, our names are on
the sign-in sheet.
(Penny:)So erase them and walk out.
(Leonard:)I can't do that.
(Howard:)Can't do what?
(Leonard:)She says take our names
(Leonard:)off the sign-in sheet
and leave.
(chuckles):
We can't do that.
Yeah.
ALL: ♪ Jingle bells, jingle
bells, jingle all the way ♪